All told, printing the pieces for this quad used about 3 kilograms of filament.
By far though, the largest print was this center section.
It used almost an entire roll of filament and took two days, even though I was printing
much faster than normal using clipper.
So two days of printing, what kind of clothes this was?
Is it running out of film?
This is a brand new spool right before I started.
Oh my god, that's heavy.
I got most of the support material out which is good, but then I realized that there were
some very unfortunate layers shifts that went on towards the end of the print.
They asked you how you were able to say that you're fine when you're not really.
I guess this is what I'd get for switching to clipper.
So since these layers shifts cause this to protrude at the end,